Lloyd E. Cotsen collection of Potter Family photographs,1865-1935: Finding Aid
Cotsen Children's Library
- Landscapes, 1880 May-1913 September; 1021 items
  - Skiddaw from Derwentwater, 1909 April; 929; 1 item 12.0 x 16.4 cm.
    Photographed during Derwentwater Hotel stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Skiddaw from / Derwent Water / Ap. 1909 / R Potter B dev.
  - North end of Derwentwater, 1909 April; 930; 1 item 12.0 x 16.3 cm.
    Photographed during Derwentwater Hotel stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Derwent Water N End / R Potter / Ap. 1909 B dev.
  - North end of Derwentwater, 1909 April; 931; 1 item 12.0 x 16.3 cm.
    Photographed during Derwentwater Hotel stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Derwent Water N End / Ap. 1909 / R Potter / B dev. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 932.
  - North end of Derwentwater, 1909 April; 932; 1 item 12.0 x 16.3 cm.
    Photographed during Derwentwater Hotel stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Derwent Water / Ap. 1909 / R Potter / B dev. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 931.
  - View from Riggs Hotel, Windermere, 1909 April; 933; 1 item 12.0 x 16.5 cm.
    Photographed during Riggs Hotel stay? Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: View from Riggs Hotel / Windermere / Ap. 1909 / B dev / R Potter.
  - Windermere from Riggs Hotel, 1909 April; 934; 1 item 12.0 x 16.3 cm.
    Photographed during Riggs Hotel stay? Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Ap. 1909 / Wmere from Riggs / Hotel / R Potter.
  - Dove's Nest, Windermere, 1909 April; 935; 1 item 11.2 x 15.7 cm.
    Photographed during Riggs Hotel stay? Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Doves Nest / Windermere / R potter / B / Ap. 1909.
  - Dove's Nest, Windermere, from Low Wood Pier, 1909 April; 936; 1 item 12.0 x 16.5 cm.
    Photographed during Riggs Hotel stay? Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Doves Nest Windermere / from Low Wood Pier / Ap. 1909 / R Potter / B.
  - Dove's Nest, Windermere, 1909 April; 937; 1 item 11.1 x 15.6 cm.
    Photographed during Riggs Hotel stay? Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Doves Nest / Windermere / Ap. 1909 / B / R Potter.
  - Low Wood, Windermere, 1909 April; 938; 1 item 12.0 x 16.5 cm.
    Photographed during Riggs Hotel stay? Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Ap. 1909 / Low Wood / R Potter / B.
  - Low Wood, Windermere, 1909 April; 939; 1 item 12.0 x 16.4 cm.
    Photographed during Riggs Hotel stay? Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Low Wood / Ap. 1909 / R Potter / B.
  - Low Wood, Windermere, 1909 April; 940; 1 item 12.0 x 16.5 cm.
  - Low Wood, Windermere, 1909 April; 941; 1 item 16.5 x 12.0 cm.
  - Low Wood, Windermere, 1909 April; 942; 1 item 11.1 x 15.7 cm.
    Photographed during Riggs Hotel stay? Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Low Wood / Ap. 1909 / R Potter / B. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 943.
  - Low Wood, Windermere, 1909 April; 943; 1 item 12.0 x 16.4 cm.
    Photographed during Riggs Hotel stay? Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Low Wood / Windermere / Ap. 1909 / R Potter B dev. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 942.
  - Windermere from Low Wood, 1909 April; 944; 1 item 11.2 x 15.7 cm.
    Photographed during Riggs Hotel stay? Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Windermere from Low Wood / Ap. 1909 / R Potter / B.
  - Windermere from Low Wood, 1909 April; 945; 1 item 12.0 x 16.3 cm.
    Photographed during Riggs Hotel stay? Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Windermere from Low Wood / Ap. 1909 / R Potter / B dev.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1909 July 17; 946; 1 item 8.3 x 10.7 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: July 17 1909 / Broad Leys / R Potter.
    Catalog number: 464
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1909 July 18; 947; 1 item 16.5 x 21.4 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: July 18 1909 / Windermere from Broad Leys / B 11 1/2 / R Potter. Forms panorama with CTSN Potter 948.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1909 July 18; 948; 1 item 16.5 x 21.4 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: July 18 1909 / Windermere from Broad Leys / B 11 1/2 / R Potter. Forms panorama with CTSN Potter 947.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1909 July 20; 949; 1 item 16.5 x 21.3 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Windermere from Broad Leys / July 20 1909 / B 11 1/2 / R Potter.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1909 July 27; 950; 1 item 16.4 x 21.4 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Windermere from Broad Leys / July 27 1909 / 11 1/2 Sp / R Potter.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1909 July 27; 951; 1 item 16.4 x 21.4 cm.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1909 July 17; 952; 1 item 12.0 x 16.3 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: July 17 1909 / Wmere from Broad Leys / B 11 1/2 / R Potter.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1909 July 27; 953; 1 item 12.0 x 16.5 cm.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1909 July 28; 954; 1 item 12.0 x 16.3 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Windermere from Broad Leys / July 28 1909 / 7 1/2 B / R Potter.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1909 July 28; 955; 1 item 11.9 x 16.5 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Windermere from Broad Leys / July 28 1909 / 7 1/2 B / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 956.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1909 July 28; 956; 1 item 11.9 x 16.5 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Windermere from Broad Leys / B July 28 1909 / 7 1/2 / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 955.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1909 July 29; 957; 1 item 12.0 x 16.5 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Windermere from / Broad Leys / July 29 1909 / B / R Potter.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1909 July 29; 958; 1 item 11.9 x 16.5 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Broad Leys / July 29 1909 / SP NTG / R Potter. Illegible technical inscription, upper right corner verso.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1909 July 30; 959; 1 item 12.0 x 16.3 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Windermere from Broad Leys / July 30 1909 / SP NTG / R Potter. Illegible technical inscription, upper right corner verso.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1909 July 30; 960; 1 item 11.9 x 16.5 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Broad Leys / July 31 1909 / NTG / R Potter. Inscribed in pencil, by Rupert Potter?, lower left corner verso: 31 N.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1909 August 7; 961; 1 item 8.3 x 10.7 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Wmere from Broad Leys / Aug 7 1909 / R Potter.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 6 am, 1909 August 8; 962; 1 item 12.0 x 16.3 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Windermere from Broad Leys / 6. am / Aug 8 1909 / NTG / R Potter.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1909 August 14; 963; 1 item 12.0 x 16.4 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Windermere from Broad Leys / Aug 14 1909 / I.O / R Potter.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1909 August 14; 964; 1 item 11.9 x 16.5 cm.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, evening, 1909 August 16; 965; 1 item 12.0 x 16.4 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Evening / Windermere from Broad Leys / Aug 16 1909 / I.O / R Potter.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1909 August 17; 966; 1 item 12.0 x 16.4 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Windermere from Broad Leys / Aug 17 1909 / I.O / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 967.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1909 August 17; 967; 1 item 12.0 x 16.4 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Windermere from Broad Leys / Aug 17 1909 / I.O / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 966.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1909 August 17; 968; 1 item 12.0 x 16.4 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Windermere from Broad Leys / Aug 17 1909 / I.O / R Potter.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1909 August 17; 969; 1 item 12.0 x 16.4 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Windermere from Broad Leys / Aug 17 1909 / I.O / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 970-971.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1909 August 17; 970; 1 item 12.0 x 16.4 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Windermere from Broad Leys / Aug 17 1909 / I.O / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 969, 971.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1909 August 17; 971; 1 item 12.0 x 16.4 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Windermere from Broad Leys / Aug 17 1909 / I.O / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 969-970.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1909 August 17; 972; 1 item 12.0 x 16.4 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Windermere from Broad Leys / Aug 17 1909 / I.O / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 973.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1909 August 17; 973; 1 item 12.0 x 16.4 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Windermere from Broad Leys / Aug 17 1909 / I.O / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 972.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1909 August 17; 974; 1 item 12.0 x 16.4 cm.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1909 August 20; 975; 1 item 16.4 x 21.3 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Windermere from Broad Leys / Aug 20 1909 / I.O 11 1/2 / R Potter.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1909 August 21; 976; 1 item 16.4 x 21.4 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Windermere from Broad Leys / Aug 21 1909 / Imp. [Orch] / R Potter.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1909 August 21; 977; 1 item 16.4 x 21.4 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Windermere from Broad Leys / Aug 21 1909 / I.O 11 1/2 / R Potter.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1909 August 21; 978; 1 item 21.4 x 16.5 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Windermere from / Broad Leys / Aug 21. 1909 / I.O 11 1/2 / R Potter.
  - Grasmere Church, 1909 August 28; 979; 1 item 8.1 x 10.1 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Two small figures sitting on a wall, possibly Beatrix and Bertram. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Grasmere Church / Aug 28 1909 / R Potter. Previous inscription, in Rupert Potter's hand, erased: Grasmere / Wordsworths Grave. Inscribed in pencil, lower left corner verso, by Rupert Potter?: 28.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1909 September 2; 980; 1 item 16.4 x 21.3 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Windermere from Broad Leys / Sep 2 1909 / I.O 11 1/2 / R Potter. Technical inscription lower left corner verso, illegible.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1909 September 2; 981; 1 item 16.4 x 21.3 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Windermere from Broad Leys / Sep 2 1909 / I.O 11 1/2 / R Potter. Technical inscription lower left corner verso, illegible. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 982-983.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1909 September 2; 982; 1 item 16.4 x 21.3 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Windermere from Broad Leys / Sep 2 1909 / I.O 11 1/2 / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 981, 983.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1909 September 2; 983; 1 item 16.4 x 21.4 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Windermere from Broad Leys / Sep. 2 1909 / I.O 11 1/2 / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 981-982.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1909 September 3; 984; 1 item 12.0 x 16.4 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Windermere / from Broad Leys / 11 1/2 I.O / Sep 3 1909 / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 985.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1909 September 3; 985; 1 item 12.0 x 16.3 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Windermere from Broad Leys / Sep 3 1909 / I.O. 11 1/2 / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 984.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1909 September 3; 986; 1 item 12.0 x 16.3 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Windermere from Broad Leys / Sep 3 1909 / I.O. 11 1/2 / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 987-989.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1909 September 3; 987; 1 item 12.0 x 16.3 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Windermere from Broad Leys / Sep 3 1909 / I.O. 11 1/2 / R Potter. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter, lower left corner verso: 3 0 11 1/2. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 986, 988-989.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1909 September 3; 988; 1 item 12.0 x 16.4 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Windermere from Broad Leys / Sep 3 1909 / I.O. 11 1/2 / R Potter. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter, lower left corner verso: 3 0 11 1/4. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 986-987, 989.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1909 September 3; 989; 1 item 12.0 x 16.4 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Windermere from Broad Leys / Sep 3 1909 / I.O. 11 1/2 / R Potter. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter, lower left corner verso: 3 0 11 1/2. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 986-988.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1909 September 10; 990; 1 item 12.0 x 16.3 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Windermere from Broad Leys / Sep. 10 1909 / I.O. 11 1/2 / R Potter. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter, lower left corner verso: Sep 10 0 11 1/2.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1909 September 10; 991; 1 item 12.0 x 16.3 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Windermere from / Broad Leys / Sep. 10 1909 / I.O. 11 1/2 / R Potter. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter, lower left corner verso: 10 11 1/2 IO.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1909 September 14; 992; 1 item 16.4 x 21.3 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Sep. 14. 1909 / Windermere from Broad Leys / O. 11 1/2 [d sh] / R Potter. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter, lower left corner verso: 14 0 11 1/2. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 993-994.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1909 September 14; 993; 1 item 16.4 x 21.3 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: 14 Sep. 1909 / Windermere from Broad Leys / O / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 992, 994. Severely creased, portions of emulsion detaching from surface of print.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1909 September 14; 994; 1 item 12.0 x 16.3 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Windermere from Broad Leys / O 11 1/2 [illegible] / R Potter. Illegible technical inscription lower left corner verso, Rupert Potter's hand. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 992-993, trimmed down.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1909 September 20; 995; 1 item 12.0 x 16.3 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Windermere from Broad Leys / 20 Sep. 1909 / R Potter / I.O. Inscribed in pencil lower left corner, Rupert Potter's hand: 20 11 1/2 0. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 996.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1909 September 20; 996; 1 item 12.0 x 16.4 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Windermere from Broad Leys / Sep 1909 / R Potter / I.O.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1909 September 20; 997; 1 item 12.0 x 16.4 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Windermere from Broad Leys / Sep 20 1909 / I.O / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 998.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1909 September 20; 998; 1 item 12.0 x 16.4 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Windermere from Broad Leys / Sep 20 1909 / I.O / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 997.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1909 September 20; 999; 1 item 12.0 x 16.4 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Broad Leys / Sep 20 1909 / R Potter.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1909 September 20; 1000; 1 item 12.0 x 16.4 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Windermere from Broad Leys / Sep 20 1909 / I.O R Potter. Inscribed in pencil lower left corner verso, by Rupert Potter: 21 0 11 1/2.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1909 September 20; 1001; 1 item 12.0 x 16.3 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Windermere from / Broad Leys / Sep 20 1909 / 0 11 1/2 / R Potter. Inscribed in pencil lower left corner verso, by Rupert Potter: 20 0 11 1/2. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 1002.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1909 September 20; 1002; 1 item 12.0 x 16.3 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Windermere from Broad Leys / Sep 20 1909 / 0 11 1/2 / R Potter. Inscribed in pencil lower left corner verso, by Rupert Potter: 0 11 1/2. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 1001.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1909 September 20; 1003; 1 item 16.4 x 21.3 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Windermere from Broad Leys / Sep 20 1909 / 0 11 1/2 / R Potter. Inscribed in pencil lower left corner verso, by Rupert Potter: 20 11 1/2 0. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 1004-1006.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1909 September 20; 1004; 1 item 16.4 x 21.3 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Windermere from Broad Leys / Sep 20 1909 / I.O / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 1003, 1005-1006.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1909 September 20; 1005; 1 item 16.4 x 21.4 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Windermere from Broad Leys / Sep. 1909 / I.O 11 1/2 / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 1003-1004, 1006.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1909 September 20; 1006; 1 item 16.4 x 21.4 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Sep. 1909 / Windermere from Broad Leys / I.O 11 1/2 / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 1003-1005.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1909 September 20; 1007; 1 item 16.4 x 21.3 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Windermere from Broad Leys / Sep 20 1909 / O 11 1/2 / R Potter. Inscribed in pencil lower left corner verso, by Rupert Potter: 20 0 11 1/2.
  - Windermere from Broad Leys, 1909 September; 1008; 1 item 8.1 x 10.6 cm.
    Photographed during Broad Leys stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Broad Leys / Sep. 1909 / NTG R Potter.
  - View from Helm, Windermere, 1910 July; 1009; 1 item 12.0 x 16.3 cm.
    Photographed during Helm Farm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: July 1910 / View from Helm / Wmere / R Potter / 11 1/2 0 [illegible]. Inscribed in pencil lower left corner verso, by Rupert Potter: [m] 31 11 1/2 0.
    Catalog number: 470
  - Patterdale, Ullswater, 1910 August 10; 1010; 1 item 16.4 x 21.4 cm.
    Photographed during Helm Farm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Aug 10 1910 / Ullswater / Patterdale / 11 1/2 i l o [d sh]. Inscribed in pencil lower left corner verso, by Rupert Potter: 10 11 1/2 o 1 l [d sh].
  - Patterdale, Ullswater, 1910 August 10; 1011; 1 item 16.4 x 21.4 cm.
    Photographed during Helm Farm stay. Groups of tiny figures at left, possibly family members? Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Aug 10 1910 / Ullswater / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 1012-1014.
  - Patterdale, Ullswater, 1910 August 10; 1012; 1 item 16.4 x 21.4 cm.
    Photographed during Helm Farm stay. Groups of tiny figures at left, possibly family members? Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Aug 10 1910 / Patterdale / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 1011, 1013-1014.
  - Patterdale, Ullswater, 1910 August 10; 1013; 1 item 16.4 x 21.3 cm.
    Photographed during Helm Farm stay. Groups of tiny figures at left, possibly family members? Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Aug 10 1910 / Ullswater / Patterdale / 11 1/2 1 l o [d sh] / R Potter. Inscribed in pencil lower left corner verso, by Rupert Potter: R10. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 1011-1012, 1014.